<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Scenic Home & Office Organizers]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Scenic Home & Office Organizers]]></description>
        <link>http://www.scenicorg.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 02:33:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://www.scenicorg.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>HOME CONTACT BLOG SHOP POLICIES    Our New Year's Resolution    To create a more organized community...  We love seeing the positive transformation of our clients' homes and lives. To see a ginormous weight lifted off of their shoulders is priceless. It is our goal to help our clients de-clutter their homes and offices so that they can get back to enjoying their lives.  Being organized can save you time, money, and stress. No more searching for lost items, missing bill payments, or stumbling over things. Your time is valuable! If your New Year's resolution is to become more organized, please call or email us. You are invited to take advantage of a FREE initial consultation. Opportunities like this don't come around often, so book a session today. Call or email us before February 1st to lock in your free initial consultation. We look forward to organizing with you!  Phone: (573) 368-8079 Email: contact@scenicorg.com    When We Say "Customized", We Mean It    September 4, 2015    Every family has their own unique organizing needs. Your lifestyle is different from everyone else's, so why should you follow the same organizing rules? Maybe you don't need a paper calendar to organize your schedule. Maybe you want something that fits your home decor. Or maybe you need custom-built garage storage, because the store-bought ones just don't cut it.  We live in a world where everything we buy is standardized, which doesn't always suit our needs. We can help with that.  We have individuals in our network that can build that custom storage rack, shelf, command center, or even spice rack! Here are a couple of projects that we have produced.     As organizers, we are innovative and creative. We know that not every person, or every home, fits the same mold. We can help you come up with an idea AND bring it to life. If you already have an idea, but just need someone to produce it, we can do that too. Call or text (573) 368-8079, or use the Contact page to get a free quote. We look forward to organizing with you!   6 Ways an Organizer Can Change Your Life August 28, 2015   1. You are moving into a new home, but you don’t have time to organize how you’d like to. Let’s face it, living out of boxes and suitcases isn’t exactly glamorous. You want to show off your shiny new abode to your family and friends, but you haven’t unpacked. Or, you want to start parking for the move, but you don’t know where to begin.  Begin by picking up that phone and calling Scenic. Many times we do promotions to make your initial consultation low-cost. We’ll help you sort out your goals, and you decide whether you want to move forward with a hands-on organizing session.  2. You need help with functionality.  You have a beautiful glass coffee table, but it quickly becomes covered with mail and magazines. You never fully enjoy your home.  Scenic can suggest creative, yet practical solutions for storage, displays, and other organization areas. We do an initial consultation with you to assess the space, and we’ll suggest solutions to fit your needs.  3. Your home office is no longer a place you want to work in. You have paperwork, receipts, mail, and files everywhere. Maybe you just get tired of reaching, straining, and stretching to get things.  We will help you file, scan, categorize, shred, and label your office to make the stressful paper disappear. We can even help you configure an office layout that promotes smooth workflow.  4. Your house isn’t a mess, but you’re wondering if there’s an easier way to stay organized. Organization isn’t a destination, it is a continuous process. As your lifestyle changes, you may need updates to keep things running smoothly.  Set up an initial, 1-hour consultation with us and we can come up with a plan, together.  5. You want to organize, but you need help coming up with a game-plan. You are a Do-It-Yourself kind of person, so you want to organize your way. You have lots of creative ideas, but you need help narrowing it down.  Let’s get together for an initial consultation, and we can narrow down your goals. We can even suggest materials that could be helpful for the project. We can give you advice on techniques that we use to keep things orderly.  6. You have kids. Your children are the light of your life, and you work hard to keep them happy. You are busy making sure they get a good education, are well nourished, and have a good social life. You don’t have much time to sort through old clothes, toys, and memorabilia that has accrued.  We will help you sort, donate, preserve, display, and store things that are collecting around your home. Not only will we do that, but we can come up with a system to stay on top of these things. Set up an initial consultation today. We’ll work around your busy schedule.   Back to School Organization Tips August 26, 2015    We know how stressful getting your kids back to school can be. Your drawers are packed with school registration papers, immunization records, and art projects. All of the information you could ever need is in there, but you can never find it fast enough. The towering pile of paperwork can quickly get out of hand. Especially when registration day comes around. Oh, the joy! We want to help out. Here are a few tips on how to control the chaos.  1. Sort Sort all of your papers into categories. The categories depend on your individual needs, but I recommend something like this… · Registration documents · Health records · Extra curricular · Grade cards · Awards · Art projects Each child should have their own stack.  2. File If you don’t have an extreme amount of paper, you can use a file folder with each child’s name on it and the year with tab dividers for each. If you simply have way too much paper, then buy an expanding file for each child, write their name and the year on the front, and write your categories on the tabs. So simple!  3. Reduce Take photos of the large or oddly shaped art projects that were so graciously gifted to you on mother’s day. It is a beautiful piece of art, and you will remember the fuzzy feelings you got even when it is in photo form. Recycle the real version, or put it into a storage container with your kid’s name on it and the year. Whatever you do to get it off of the kitchen table!  4. Set up a command Center This is my favorite trick of all time. Every day, you may come home and get a plethora of grade cards, art projects, waivers to sign, homework to check, but what do you do with these things? You need to create a visible filing system where you can see what you have. My command center includes a place for immediate use documents, and a place for later use documents. For example, your bank statements, tax forms, grade cards, and health records can go into the later use, while your coupons, bills, field trip waivers, and anything that needs a response can go into the immediate use section. You’ll always remember to pay the trash bill if it is right in front of you. You can periodically empty the later use documents into your permanent filing system when time allows. Here are some examples.      There are so many great ways to get organized. Your friendly professional organizer can even help you get organized with major projects that you simply aren’t able to do yourself! Contact us now for a free quote. Photo Credit: (Left bbeingcool.com) (Right unoriginalmom.com)   3 Springfield Charities & Items They Accept July 24, 2015    Our Springfield, MO community has great need for donated items. When organizing your home, you may find you have a plethora of good, useable items that you don't need anymore. You shouldn't throw them away, instead you should give them new life by donating them to charities. Here are 3 perfect examples of charities that will graciously accept your unwanted household items. Harmony House: Springfield's domestic violence shelter. Box Fans Bathroom Cups Clorox Wipes/All Purpose Cleaner New make up Hair dryers/Curling Irons Men’s Hygiene Products Silverware & Cooking Utensils Body Spray/Perfume Household Items Toilet paper and paper towels Linens – sheet sets and towel sets Cleaning supplies, mops, brooms and vacuum cleaners Kitchen items – dishes, pots, pans and utensils Living room and bedroom furniture Clothing and Hygiene Women’s Jeans sizes 11 and up Women’s shirts and sweatshirts Women’s pajamas Women’s underwear Tampons and pads Shampoo and Conditioner Toothpaste & Toothbrushes Deodorant Over the counter medication Toys Boys and girls clothing Boys and girls pajamas Boys and girls underwear Over the counter children’s medication For donation drop off location and more ways you can contribute, visit their website! https://www.myharmonyhouse.org Habitat for Humanity: Springfield's housing organization. Appliances Bathroom Bedding Blinds Brick Cabinets Carpet Ceiling Fans Commercial Donations Doors  Drapery/Curtains Drywall/Sheetrock Electrical Fixtures Furniture Glass Hardware Lawn Mowers & Outdoor Power Equipment Light Fixtures Lumber Mirrors Paint and Stai Plumbing Fixtures Roofing Shelving Sheet Goods Siding Sinks Televisions & Computer Monitors Tile & Flooring Toilets Tools Vehicles Windows For a more detailed list of items & restrictions, visit their website! https://habitatspringfieldmo.org/restore/donate-items/accepted-items  The Kitchen: Springfield's non profit organization in a fight to end homelessness. Couches Loveseats Coffee tables End tables Chairs Adjustable bed frames Dressers http://www.thekitcheninc.org/donate.html  As you can see, there are many places to choose from to support through charitable giving. And if you're hesitant to let go of an item that you love but no longer use, give it to someone else. Your donations will be put to good use!  The Kitchen's Daily Needs List  3 3 Big-Impact Recycling Hacks June 25, 2015   Commonly recycled items include paper, plastic, glass, and metal. Other recycling categories exist, but many people have these four main groups, according to springfieldmo.gov.  Some of these recycling bins can be bulky, and difficult to keep organized in your home. We can help you f find a good way to tame the chaos! Here are a few clever ways to organize your recycling. 1. Stack it up! Y You can build racks to stack your recycling bins, but accessing those bins without having to pull them out of their cubby can be a nuisance. Especially if you are teaching your little ones how t to recycle. You can easily toss your recyclables in,and have much more floor space. Find it here:http://www.walmart.com/ip/United-Comb-An-Novelty-Blue-Recycling-Stack-Bin-SB0028-Pack-of-6/26078682   We also love these inexpensive choices from the container store. Find it here: http://www.containerstore.com/shop/trashRecycling/recycling       2. Hang it If you need all of the floor space you can get, you can always try hanging your regular recycling bins. Familyhandyman.com gives a description on a DIY version of this method. Personally, I’d probably stick with hanging only my light-weight bins. Find it here:http://familyhandyman.com/storage-organization/garage-organization-create-recycle-bin-hangers/view-all   3. Hide it If you don’t like the bulky bins, you can always hide them. You can create a big-impact by using colorful bins, or painting your iKea bins to match your home. Here are some really fun products below...     Find it here: http://www.ikea.com/us/en/catalog/products/S09102532 Find it here: http://www.containerstore.com/shop/trashRecycling/recycling My favorite recycling hack has to be these creative DIY projects, using Cabinets from iKea. Your recyclables will be as good as invisible. If I could, I would have ALL of my garbage and recycling bins done this way :).     Photo credit: ikeahackers.net There you have it! Get clever with your recycling storage. I hope these solutions help you take control of your living space. Do you have awesome & creative recycling solutions? Let us know by messaging us on facebook. We’d love to hear your ideas.  Connect with us now!: https://www.facebook.com/scenichomeandoffice   10 Alternatives to Your Spring Cleaning Checklist June 18, 2015     When your Spring Cleaning Checklist isn’t working out as planned, you may need a little something else. You can always clean, so why not take this time to organize instead. We've taken a traditional Spring Cleaning Checklist and translated it into a list of what your home really needs. 1. Vacuum and shampoo the rugs Translation: pick up all of the shoes sitting on the rugs in your home, and organize them. You can throw out the ones that are damaged and sell or donate the ones you don’t wear or your children grew out of. What do you do with the ones you keep? You can use; Shoe racks Over-the-door closet organizers Flip flop closet hangers  2. Dust books and shelves Translation: send your overdue books back to the library! Find a new home for books that you are never going to read again. If looking at your overflowing bookshelf doesn’t make you happy, then change it. One thing that I’ve learned to do with my shelf is take each book, one by one, and decide if I’m ever going to read it again. If not, I can donate it, sell it, or gift it to a friend.  That goes for knick knacks as well. If a certain knick knack doesn’t bring you a spark of fond memories or happiness when you look at it, then you might not need it anymore. It has served its purpose, and someone else might have more use for it than you do.  3. Clean the furniture Translation: Take all of the cushions off of your couches, and dig out the toys, loose change, candy wrappers, etc. that you find. Put the loose change in a savings jar, throw out all the trash, and then decide what to do with those really old (does my kid even want these anymore?) toys.  4. Wax the tables and wooden surfaces Translation: You can’t really wax your tables with paper, pens, and any other assortment of items all over it. Sort these items into categories. For example; Office supplies Children’s artwork Bills Groceries/food items Then, put everything away, category by category, until your tables are all cleared off. You can start eating dinner at the table again!  5. Clean window treatments You probably should clean your window treatments. This would be a good time to throw them in the laundry. It will help reduce the amount of dust in the air, and allergies! Achoo!  6. Sweep, mop, and wax the floors T Translation: Pick everything up off of the floors. Sort them into categories like; Laundry Trash Toys Hygiene/ bathroom items Dishes Pens, crayons, markers, art supplies Things you need to file (receipts, insurance policies, warranties) Then, work on putting everything away, category by category, until you can walk around without stepping on Legos.  7. Dust refrigerator coils Translation: Instead, you can go through everything in your fridge. Throw out anything that is past its expiration (whether it is moldy or not). Sort your items into categories like dairy, meats, fruits, vegetables, and condiments.  8. Switch out blankets This one is actually a good one. Swap your microfiber sheets for cotton or silk ones. Change out your down comforter for a summer quilt.  9. Mattresses  While you’re at it, you can flip or turn your mattresses, so they don’t wear too much on one side or another. You’ll save money because it will reduce wear and tear.  10. Clean out the closets If you don’t feel like going through every single item in your closet, at least switch out your fall and winter clothes for spring and summer ones. Store your coats, heavy jackets, gloves, scarves, and hats together in a tote. Put long sleeves, sweaters, thermals, and sweat pants into another. Put the totes away so they aren’t in the way. Don’t forget to label your totes, or you will forget that you even had the stuff to begin with.  One way to get out of doing this every season is to do a little at a time, every day. If you set aside 5 minutes to sort through & file your mail every day, or 10 minutes to clear the floors then your home will start to look better and better.    7 Steps to Get Organized June 11, 2015    You have several areas in your home that need organizing, how do you know where to begin? It can be overwhelming, but these few tips will help you conquer the task. You can start by answering these questions: Which area is used most often, or has the most traffic? Will organizing this area give you more space or resources to aid in completing your other projects? (For example: organizing my bedroom will give me more room to organize my closet later). Is this project critical in order to get something else done?  1. Pick Your Project Use the questions listed above! You want to create a big impact with each organization project. This will help you see the most progress. It might not be what you WANT to do, but it’s what you need to do first.  2. Set Goals What do you want to accomplish during your organizing project? Your goals need to be realistic, and specific. For example, I will sort through all of my clothing and decide what to keep, donate, and throw away by 5pm tomorrow.  3. Make Room You will need a clean, clear work space to organize with. Whether you are organizing paper, files, jewelry, clothing, or even dishes. It will save the stress of trying to work around other messes, and you will be less likely to lose things.  4. Categorize Sort your items into categories. This will make it easier to put similar things close to one another, and you will be less likely to forget where you put them.  5. Give it a Home Each item in your home or office should have a permanent “home,” or a place that it goes back to EVERY TIME it is removed. If an item doesn’t have a home, you need to decide whether you need it or not. If you DO need it, create a home for it.  6. Stay on Track Do you often find yourself doing side-projects that you never intended to do? Put this side-project on the back burner for now. The fewer projects that you are involved with at one time, the faster you will be able to to complete your main project. It will keep you more motivated to know that you’re knocking projects out, one-by-one.  7. Maintain Take 5 minutes a day to file your mail, 10 minutes to fold laundry, or put things back exactly where you found them. You will have much more time to live a stress-free, clutter-free life if you do a little every day.    What Does a Professional Organizer Do? June 1, 2015     Many people ask us, what does a professional organizer do?  Not all organizing consultations are dramatic makeovers like you see on TV. Most jobs are done with only one or two organizers. Professional organizers will come to your home or office and help you create an organizing system, while teaching you valuable, lifelong organization skills that will help you STAY organized.  Do I have to throw things away?  A professional organizer won’t force you to get rid of anything, or throw something away without your permission. You will always get to make the final decision on what happens to your belongings. It’s all a part of the process! With you in the driver’s seat, we are able to create a customized system that will work for you, long-term. Your organizer will also guide you through making difficult decisions.  Do I have to be there while you organize?  An organizer will organize along side you, so that you can learn methods to stay organized on your own. Think of it as a learning experience. You get pointers along the way, coaching, and mentoring in addition to a gorgeous, new, workable area of your home/office. Some clients really get into the organizing and have fun with it, which makes it an awesome experience for both of us!  Is it like a cleaning service?  Professional organizers typically don’t clean, (sweep, mop, sanitize, wash laundry or dishes) for you. There are cleaning services specifically for that. We help you develop and implement creative solutions to your space. We want to help transfer our knowledge to you in a hands-on environment, so you can gain new skills to live a clutter-free life.  How long will it take?  That depends, how big is the space? How much stuff do you have? Do you take more time to make decisions? A professional organizer will want to view the area, and may suggest a package that will work best for you. To schedule a 1-hour consultation, contact us. We’ll be able to help you come up with a game plan for organizing your space. To find a list of services, visit our Services page.     4002 W. TRACY ST. SPRINGFIELD, MO 65807  E: CONTACT@SCENICORG.COM  P: 573.368.8079</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.scenicorg.com/home-contact-blog-shop-policies-our-new-years-resolution/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7f9b5fdb-8bc5-432e-8a1d-2e3f15335c69</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 02:32:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>HOME CONTACT BLOG SHOP POLICIES  Scenic Home & Office Policies      Minimum Booking Requirement There is a 4-hour minimum for organizing sessions. We've determined this to be the prime amount of time for our clients to begin to see real results.  Satisfaction Guarantee If you're not satisfied upon completion of your service, Scenic Home & Office Organizers will return for a free session to better meet your needs and work with you until you're completely satisfied with the results. Failure to make a claim in writing within seven business days implies that Client fully accepts the completed work. Travel fee, when applicable, still applies.   Travel Policy We travel up to 50 miles from Springfield, MO free of charge. All necessary travel expenses will be discussed and agreed upon prior to service completion. Contact us by phone or e-mail to find out about specific travel expenses. And just like that, Scenic will be wherever you need them to be!  Payment Policy  We accept payment by cash, check (payable to Scenic Home & Office Organizers), money order, and debit/credit card. Payments for individual services or service packages are due at the end of the first session. Billable time begins once a Scenic Home & Office organizer arrives at your home or office location and ends when each session is completed. ﻿ Check Policy  By using a check for payment, you agree to the following terms: In the event that your check is dishonored or returned for any reason, you authorize us to electronically (or by paper draft) re-present the check to your bank account for collection of the amount of the check, plus any applicable fees as permitted by state law. For more information, please call Re$ubmitIt® at (866) 860-5906.      4002 W. TRACY ST. SPRINGFIELD, MO 65807  E: CONTACT@SCENICORG.COM  P: 573.368.8079</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.scenicorg.com/home-contact-blog-shop-policies-scenic-home-and-office-polici/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0886db94-e23e-44b7-9e6f-45b56fa9c319</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 02:32:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>HOME CONTACT BLOG SHOP POLICIES  Services    Every organization project is unique. We strive to come up with customized organization systems that work specifically for you. See below for some of the services we offer.    Custom-Built Organizing Systems      Scenic Home & Office Organizers can custom-build a range of organizing systems to suit your needs!    Meet your Command Center    Command centers are great for keeping your home and office organized. For home - keep track of bills, coupons, recipes, and much more. For work - keep your reports, projects, and other important items organized and ready at hand.    Size Pick the size that's right for you. We can make yours in any size to best suit your needs!  Design Have a pattern, theme, or certain materials in mind? Let's incorporate them.  Color Let us know your preferred colors and we will work to find exact matches.    Have Another Organizing Project in Mind?    We can create all sorts of organizing systems that cater to many needs and areas. Garage storage, closet systems, kid's play rooms, kitchens, offices - let us know your needs and what we can create for you. We're your one stop, custom organizing shop!      4002 W. TRACY ST. SPRINGFIELD, MO 65807  E: CONTACT@SCENICORG.COM  P: 573.368.8079</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.scenicorg.com/home-contact-blog-shop-policies-services-every-organizat/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">81d2bc46-85d3-442c-b044-6ee946b42a9e</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 02:32:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>HOME CONTACT BLOG SHOP POLICIES  MEET YOUR ORGANIZERS    Erik & Charlene Kean are a team of two professional organizers based in Springfield, MO. Our mission is to work with you to design customized, functional home & office organization systems.  Together we will create a stress free environment so you can work efficiently and effectively. We want to help you set your own goals, and be able to reach them! Check our our services page to find out how we can help you.   SUCCESS STORIES      BASEMENT / GARAGE OVERHAUL    KITCHEN MAKEOVER    LIVING ROOM SHUFFLE    LARGE COMMAND CENTER    MEDIUM COMMAND CENTER    SPICE UP YOUR KITCHEN      4002 W. TRACY ST. SPRINGFIELD, MO 65807  E: CONTACT@SCENICORG.COM  P: 573.368.8079</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.scenicorg.com/home-contact-blog-shop-policies-meet-your-organizers-eri/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">762761e2-38ca-478c-9f88-91463087a126</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 02:31:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/a8dc9342-b1e9-45a2-81a8-ca6856f83485.png">]]></description>
            <link>http://www.scenicorg.com/9231828b-150f-47da-9ec0-41d84f866621/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9231828b-150f-47da-9ec0-41d84f866621</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 00:44:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>