<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Scenic Home & Office Organizers]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Scenic Home & Office Organizers]]></description>
        <link>http://www.scenicorg.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 02:33:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://www.scenicorg.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>HOME CONTACT BLOG SHOP POLICIES  Scenic Home & Office Policies      Minimum Booking Requirement There is a 4-hour minimum for organizing sessions. We've determined this to be the prime amount of time for our clients to begin to see real results.  Satisfaction Guarantee If you're not satisfied upon completion of your service, Scenic Home & Office Organizers will return for a free session to better meet your needs and work with you until you're completely satisfied with the results. Failure to make a claim in writing within seven business days implies that Client fully accepts the completed work. Travel fee, when applicable, still applies.   Travel Policy We travel up to 50 miles from Springfield, MO free of charge. All necessary travel expenses will be discussed and agreed upon prior to service completion. Contact us by phone or e-mail to find out about specific travel expenses. And just like that, Scenic will be wherever you need them to be!  Payment Policy  We accept payment by cash, check (payable to Scenic Home & Office Organizers), money order, and debit/credit card. Payments for individual services or service packages are due at the end of the first session. Billable time begins once a Scenic Home & Office organizer arrives at your home or office location and ends when each session is completed. ﻿ Check Policy  By using a check for payment, you agree to the following terms: In the event that your check is dishonored or returned for any reason, you authorize us to electronically (or by paper draft) re-present the check to your bank account for collection of the amount of the check, plus any applicable fees as permitted by state law. For more information, please call Re$ubmitIt® at (866) 860-5906.      4002 W. TRACY ST. SPRINGFIELD, MO 65807  E: CONTACT@SCENICORG.COM  P: 573.368.8079</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.scenicorg.com/home-contact-blog-shop-policies-scenic-home-and-office-polici/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0886db94-e23e-44b7-9e6f-45b56fa9c319</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 02:32:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>HOME CONTACT BLOG SHOP POLICIES  Services    Every organization project is unique. We strive to come up with customized organization systems that work specifically for you. See below for some of the services we offer.    Custom-Built Organizing Systems      Scenic Home & Office Organizers can custom-build a range of organizing systems to suit your needs!    Meet your Command Center    Command centers are great for keeping your home and office organized. For home - keep track of bills, coupons, recipes, and much more. For work - keep your reports, projects, and other important items organized and ready at hand.    Size Pick the size that's right for you. We can make yours in any size to best suit your needs!  Design Have a pattern, theme, or certain materials in mind? Let's incorporate them.  Color Let us know your preferred colors and we will work to find exact matches.    Have Another Organizing Project in Mind?    We can create all sorts of organizing systems that cater to many needs and areas. Garage storage, closet systems, kid's play rooms, kitchens, offices - let us know your needs and what we can create for you. We're your one stop, custom organizing shop!      4002 W. TRACY ST. SPRINGFIELD, MO 65807  E: CONTACT@SCENICORG.COM  P: 573.368.8079</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.scenicorg.com/home-contact-blog-shop-policies-services-every-organizat/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">81d2bc46-85d3-442c-b044-6ee946b42a9e</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 02:32:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>HOME CONTACT BLOG SHOP POLICIES  MEET YOUR ORGANIZERS    Erik & Charlene Kean are a team of two professional organizers based in Springfield, MO. Our mission is to work with you to design customized, functional home & office organization systems.  Together we will create a stress free environment so you can work efficiently and effectively. We want to help you set your own goals, and be able to reach them! Check our our services page to find out how we can help you.   SUCCESS STORIES      BASEMENT / GARAGE OVERHAUL    KITCHEN MAKEOVER    LIVING ROOM SHUFFLE    LARGE COMMAND CENTER    MEDIUM COMMAND CENTER    SPICE UP YOUR KITCHEN      4002 W. TRACY ST. SPRINGFIELD, MO 65807  E: CONTACT@SCENICORG.COM  P: 573.368.8079</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.scenicorg.com/home-contact-blog-shop-policies-meet-your-organizers-eri/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">762761e2-38ca-478c-9f88-91463087a126</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 02:31:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/a8dc9342-b1e9-45a2-81a8-ca6856f83485.png">]]></description>
            <link>http://www.scenicorg.com/9231828b-150f-47da-9ec0-41d84f866621/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9231828b-150f-47da-9ec0-41d84f866621</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 00:44:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>